yellow.co.nz 2018-12-21

# Yellow Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you might provide via any of our websites or mobile applications (each, a “Property”), or otherwise. This policy explains how Yellow Pages Group Limited (“we”, “us” or “our”) manage your information. 

## Your information

You acknowledge and agree that we may collect information about you. This may be:

  * provided by you;
  * obtained or derived from Property usage information (whether through tracking your click behaviour or otherwise);
  * obtained or derived from aggregated data not relating to you personally, such as the measuring of traffic relating to our Properties; and/or
  * provided by third parties.

At times, if you do not provide certain information, we may not be able to provide services to you and/or certain functionality on the Properties may not be available.

## Use and sharing of information

We collect and use your information to:

  * generally operate our business;
  * provide you and others with, and improve, our Properties, products and services;
  * inform you about our Properties, products and services, and any changes thereof;
  * administer our contests, promotions, surveys and other services;
  * obtain your feedback or views about our Properties, products and services;
  * respond to any queries, feedback or other correspondence from you;
  * gain an understanding of your needs;
  * prevent and detect any misuse of, or fraudulent activities involving, any of our Properties, products or services; and/or
  * maintain and develop our business systems and infrastructure, including testing and upgrading of these systems.

Personal information may be shared with our officers, employees, contractors, agents, professional advisors, our related companies, and third parties (including our customers, suppliers or commercial partners) in relation to the purposes described above. We take reasonable steps to ensure that any third parties are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

We may also share your personal information as required by law, court order, regulatory authority or the listing rules of any stock exchange, to exercise our legal rights, in the event of a dispute or legal claim, and to defend against legal proceedings (threatened or actual).

We collect and use non-personal information to:

  * provide our customers or suppliers with marketing or promotional materials regarding our products and services; and/or
  * assist our staff in providing tailored sales offers to our customers.

## Accessing and correcting personal information

Under the Privacy Act 1993, you have rights of access to and correction of personal information that we hold in relation to you as an individual. There are certain grounds on which we may refuse access or correction requests (for example, where such information cannot be readily retrieved), and we reserve the right to require payment of our reasonable costs in relation to the access to and correction of your personal information.

To protect your privacy and the privacy of others, you accept that we may require you to verify your identity before we can give you access to, or change, your personal information.

## Links

Our Properties may provide links to other websites or mobile applications. Please note that such destinations may have different security and privacy policies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for any information that you divulge to such destinations or how their owners or operators collect, use or disclose such information.

## Cookies

To help us provide the best possible services for users and customers, we collect and store information about the way our Properties are used (such as the number and type of electronic devices connecting to each Property, the location and any unique IDs provided by those devices, the operating systems and browsers used by those devices, and which parts of our Properties are being viewed or used). This may include sending a "cookie" to your device. A cookie is a message given to an internet browser by a web server. The browser stores the message in a text file. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This identifies your device uniquely but does not harm your device and does not identify you.

Our Properties use one type of cookie for reporting on the use of the Property, and another type of cookie to provide you with certain functionality (such as displaying content that is relevant to you, or enabling you to retain search queries). Cookies will be sent to your device the first time you visit one of our Properties. If you do not wish to have a cookie placed on your device, please disable cookies via your internet browser’s settings menu.

## Advertisements

We may use a third-party to serve advertising when you use our Properties. They may use information about your use of our Properties (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number) to provide advertisements that may be of interest to you. When serving such advertisements, they may place, or recognise, a unique cookie on your device. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices for avoiding the use of your information, please visit <https://support.google.com/adsense/troubleshooter/1631343>.

## Nielsen//NetRatings

We use the Nielsen//NetRatings counting system to track common entry and exit points for our Properties, compiling anonymous information about usage of our Properties, and randomly and anonymously surveying users of our Properties. To do this, our Properties may include a small piece of code on each page which accumulates these statistics. For more information and to view Nielson//Net Ratings’ privacy policy, please visit <http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs>.

## Security

Although we use safeguards to protect your personal information against theft, loss or unauthorised access, use, modification, disclosure or disposal, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. We do not warrant the security of information you transmit or receive through our Properties, and these activities are conducted at your own risk.

## Emails

By registering an account with us via our Properties or by providing us with your email address, you consent to receiving commercial emails from us or on our behalf, from our related companies and/or from third parties, unless you expressly reject such consent at that time, or until you opt-out of receiving such commercial emails by using the unsubscribe facility provided therein or via certain of our Properties. We may always send you non-commercial emails.

## Terms of Use

Our [Terms of Use](https://yellow.co.nz/yellow-terms-and-conditions/) apply in addition to this Privacy Policy. In the event of any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, the Terms of Use prevail to the extent permitted at law.

## Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy, by adding, changing or removing terms at any time. Any change applies from the time it is published on the relevant Property. You should check from time to time to see if this Privacy Policy has changed. Your continued use of a Property confirms your acceptance of its terms.

## Contact us

If you have any questions about the privacy of your personal information please [contact us](https://yellow.co.nz/contact-us/).
